export const EnglishQuestions = [
    // ... previous questions
  
    {
      question: "She _____ her hair cut yesterday.",
      options: ['got', 'gets', 'will get', 'getting'],
      correct: 1,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "I _____ be able to finish this project by Friday.",
      options: ['will', 'can', 'could', 'might'],
      correct: 0,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "If I _____ more time, I would travel the world.",
      options: ['have', 'had', 'will have', 'would have'],
      correct: 1,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "The children _____ playing in the garden when it started to rain.",
      options: ['were', 'was', 'are', 'is'],
      correct: 0,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "She _____ read this book before.",
      options: ['has', 'have', 'had', 'having'],
      correct: 2,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "I _____ to the beach every summer.",
      options: ['go', 'goes', 'went', 'will go'],
      correct: 1,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "They _____ dinner when I called.",
      options: ['were eating', 'are eating', 'will be eating', 'have eaten'],
      correct: 0,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "I _____ my homework already.",
      options: ['finished', 'finish', 'will finish', 'have finished'],
      correct: 3,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "She _____ be a doctor when she grows up.",
      options: ['wants', 'want', 'wanted', 'will want'],
      correct: 0,
      marked:-1,
    },
    {
      question: "I _____ to the movies last night.",
      options: ['went', 'go', 'will go', 'have gone'],
      correct: 0,
      marked:-1,
    },
    // Add more questions here...
  ];
  